A Guide to the Huddle Family Papers, 1796-1953
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
- Series VI. Black Lick Township Records. 1870-1875., 41 folders.
  Folder 21 and Folder 22 contain Overseer of the Poor account statements dating 1870-1875, Folder 23 through Folder 25 contain claims dating 1870 to 1875. Folder 26 contains the bond of Dr. John D. Stuart for his services. Ephraim Buck served as Overseer of the Poor. As such he reviewed various claims from residents and businesses who provided care to indigent citizens. He also regularly supervised accounts established with businessed and individuals who provided regular services to paupers. Businesses often provided clothing and physicians medical care.
  Folder 27 through Folder 30 contains bonds for District One, District Two, District Three, and District Four for the Overseers of the Roads. Folders 31 contains a list of road hands. Folder 32 through Folder 33 contain account statement and reports from 1870 to 1875. Folder 34 through Folder 36 contains claims for the Overseers of the Roads. Folder 37 contains miscelleneous receipts; Folder 38 contains list of delinquent taxpayers. Folder 39 contains an order book dated 1870-1875; Folder 40 a land book dated 1873; and Folder 41 contains receipts from the 2008 Addendum.
- Series VII. Correspondence - James Layfayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1870-1878, Undated., 11 folders.
  Please see Beverly Repass Hoch's James Lafayette Buck Letters, 1870-1878, While a Student at Roanoke College, Salem, Virginia for a complete analysis of letters. Hoch annotated and transcribed letters written by James Lafayette Buck from Roanoke College to Isaac Newton Huddle in Rural Retreat, Virginia between 1870 and 1878.
  James Lafayette Buck was born in Wythe County, Virginia, on 19 September 1846. The son of John Buck and Catherine Philippi Buck, he served in the Civil War and then entered Roanoke Collegte in 1870. It was then that he started a long correspondence with Isaac Newton Huddle. Buck graduated from Roanoke College in June 1875 and seminary in Salem, Virginia three years later. He then served as an ordained Lutheran pastor at Zion Church in Roanoke County, Virginia. Buck married Callie Louise Cobb in 1883. Rev. Buck served churches in Virginia, North Carolina, Pennsylvania, South Carolina, and Florida. He died in 1920 in Jacksonville, Florida.
  - Folder 1. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1870., 6 items.
  - Folder 2. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. January - March 1871., 8 items.
  - Folder 2. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1870., 6 items.
  - Folder 3. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. April - December 1871., 8 items.
  - Folder 4. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1872., 11 items.
  - Folder 5. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1873., 11 items.
  - Folder 6. Jamse Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1874., 9 items.
  - Folder 7. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1875., 11 items.
  - Folder 8. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1876., 5 items.
  - Folder 9. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1877., 8 items.
  - Folder 10. James Lafayette Buck to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1878, Undated., 4 items.
  - Flder 11. Photographs of John Christian Buck House. Undated., 7 items.
- Financial Records, 2006 Addendum. 1852-1903., 3 folders.
  Beverly Repass Hoch dontated two account books and several loose papers relating to the Black Lick Township in January 2006.
  - Folder 1. Account Book. 1881-1897., 1 item; 97 p.; name index.
    This account ledger records financial and barter transactions such as wheat, hay, potatoes, corn, cabbage, eggs, flax seed, bacon, mutton, and labor (drilling, hauling, and farming). Names include: David C. Jones, Eli Huddle, James A Huddle, E. P. Dudley, D. S. Dudley, Jesse C. Pope, John D. Yonce, Henry Woods Fisher, Harrison BOlt, Amandus Crigger, Catherine Dutton, R. D. Candler, Reese Whitley, Rev. E Studebaker, W. B. Williams, and Isaac N. Huddle.
  - Folder 2. Account Book. 1894 - 1903., 1 item; fragment; pages numbered 343 to 478; name index on p. 343.
    This account book fragment records financial and barter transactions including cabbage, livestock, labor (farming, threshing), hay, and other crops. Names include: Kellus R. Fisher, James Lambert, W. F> Whitley, F. G. Hudson, A. J. Weaver, George E. Rhudy, F. H. Camron, C. B. Davis, John Harrelton, H. H. Bridges Lindamood, J. L. Buck, J. J. Scherer, S. G. Howe, E. W. Jones, Harrison Mays, H. D. Lefler, and M. C. Lambert.
  - Folder 3. Black Lick Township Reords and Miscellaneous Financial Records. 1852, 1859, 1871-1874, Undated., 17 items.
    This folder contains several financial documents relating to the Black Lick Township of Which Isaac Huddle was a clerk. Records include: 1852 statement of account between Terracy Musser and D. F. Martin; 1859 account statement of Martin S. Steffy for estate of John Staley. Black Lick Township documents include: 1871 account statement between H. H. Holbrook and Black Lick Township; 1872 account statement of Black Lick Township with Gibboney & Sons; 1872 list of delinquent taxpayers; 1872 account statement between J. G. Kegley and Black Lick Township; 1873 account statement between H. C. Earhart and Black Lick Township; 1873 settlement between James W. Repass and Isaac N. Huddle; 1873 promissory note between L. F. Cooper et al and Township; 1874 statement of collections recieved; 1874 list of claims allowed by the Black Lick Township; 1874 account statement between H. H. Holbrook and Black Lick Township Road District; 1874 statement between Black Lick Township and S. Y. Cooper, Overseer of Roads, 1874 list of claims allowed by the Black Lick Township; undated list of allowed claims; and undated list of road hands in District No. 4, Black Lick Township.